It is the turbulent Sengoku period.
어지러운 전국 시대.
Warlords keep on fighting day and night over Jipangu State, where Karakuri people live.
카라쿠리인이 사는 지팡구국에서는 군웅할거하여 밤낮으로 접전이 계속되고
Karakuri martial artists were sharpening their swords, dreaming of victory and honor.
카라쿠리 무예가들도 승리와 영광을 꿈꾸며 맹렬히 싸우고 있었다.
And now, a wild hero has arrived, seeking to be the number one Karakuri martial artist!
그리고 지금, 카라쿠리 무예가 제일을 꿈꾸는 터무니없는 영웅이 탄생했다!
Musashi is here-dasu!
무사시 등장이오!
Karakuri Kengouden
카라쿠리 검호전: 무사시 로드
A man always dreams of the day
사내는 언제나 세계 한가운데서
in the center of the world to become
제일 강해질 날을
AH! AH! the strongest
아! 아! 꿈꿔라
Raise the sword of your heart high to the wide sky
마음의 칼을 넓은 하늘로 번쩍 쳐들어
Raise the curtain to the road of adventure
모험의 길의 막을 연다
A skilled swordsman roams on Jipangu State
지팡구국을 떠도는 검호
His name is Musashi, a Karakuri man
그 이름은 카라쿠리인 무사시
Go! Fight!
가라! 싸워라!
The sound of fierce duels
격렬한 승부의 소리는
makes life dazzling
눈부신 인생
Battles of yesterdays make you stronger today
싸웠던 어제보다도 오늘 강해진다
Martial Arts! Dual Blade Musashi
무예! 이도류 무사시
Tomorrow will be glorious
내일은 빛난다
The sound of fierce duels
격렬한 승부의 소리는
makes life dazzling
눈부신 인생
Fight the utmost with the stillness
싸우는 한껏 고요함과 함께
Martial Arts! Dual Blade Musashi
무예! 이도류 무사시
His eyes shined! Musashi!
미간이 반짝였다 무사시!!
Once running away, Musashi managed to have an extra match against Jūbee.
도망치던 무사시는 주베와의 번외 시합을 벌이게 되었지만
But he suffered a complete defeat from the secret sword of Yagyūshinkageryū.
야규신카게류의 비검 앞에 완전히 패배의 쓴맛을 보았다.
Musashi left, dispirited. Waiting for him was Hanzō's frightening trap.
의기소침해 바깥으로 나온 무사시를 기다리고 있던 것은 한조의 무서운 함정이었다.
Go Out at Once!
카라쿠리 검호 총출격
The semi-finals match between Kojirō and Ushiwaka's begins soon!
이제 대회는 준결승, 코지로와 우시와카의 대결입니다!
Our newspaper is faster than anybody else! Buy 'em!
어디보다도 빠른 우리 회사 신보 삽쇼, 삽쇼!
He's pretty fast.
꽤나 재빠른 놈이군.
What's wrong, Kojirō? Is he too strong for ya?
뭐하나, 코지로! 옴싹달싹하질 못하나!
In front of Ushiwaka's incessant sword technique derived from crow-billed tengu, even the skilled Kojirō fails to make a move.
우시와카의 끝없는 까마귀천구에게 이어받은 필승 검법 앞에서 그 대단한 코지로도 손발을 꼼짝이질 못한다.
No matter how tricky it was though, Kojirō does not give up.
묘해 보였지만, 이대로 포기할 코지로가 아니었다.
Got him!
보였다!
Stop!
거기까지!
Match set!
승부 났소!
Great as always, Kojirō.
코지로, 대단하구먼.
Meanwhile, Musashi is trapped in Hanzō's mansion.
그 동안, 한조의 저택에 잡힌 무사시는...
Anyone!
아무나!
Is anyone there-dasu?!
아무나 있소?!
Can you hear me-dasu?
들리긴 하오?!
I have something to say-dasu!
할 말이 있소!
Shut up, you brat!
시끄럽다, 이 애새끼가!
If you don't shut up, I'll chop you up!
닥치지 않으면 썰어버린다!
Chop me up if you can-dasu!
베려면 베어 보시오!
So what, you bastard!
뭐래, 이 새끼가!
You all deceived me and arranged an execution without me even knowing it! Unforgivable-dasu!
날 속이고 멋대로 사형을 정하다니 절대 용서할 수 없소!
It's Lord Hanzō who made the decision. Your struggles are futile!
한조 님이 정했다. 버둥쳐도 소용없다!
I never did something bad-dasu!
난 나쁜 짓 따위 하지 않았소!
Even Boss Zenigatan knows that!
제니가탄 두목도 알고 있소!
Who cares?
관계 없어, 그런 거.
That's nonsense-dasu! I cannot be executed-dasu!
그런 게 어디 있소! 난 절대 사형받을 수는 없소!
Yeah, right!
멋대로 지껄여라!
I'm getting out of here-dasu!
나 여기서 나가겠소!
I want to see the final match-dasu!
결승전을 보고 싶소!
That's enough!
작작 좀 해라!
I thought he could be over there, but I guess I was wrong.
혹시나 했지만 제 감이 틀렸던 모양이니...
Right. There's no way Musashi would have gone to watch the competition, when he couldn't even enter one.
그래, 시합에도 나가지 못한 무사시가 조용히 구경에 올 리가 없지.
That's right.
그렇네요.
He was so eager...
그렇게나 의욕이 넘쳤으니까...
Musashi almost made it to the martial arts competition, just to be a fool at the last moment.
그래도 하찮은 짓을 해서 무예 대회를 헛것으로 만들었군, 무사시 놈.
Musashi, where did you go?
무사시 씨, 대체 어디로 가 버린 거에요?
Do you have any plans?
지금부터 어쩔 셈이죠?
Don't worry! Considering all that happened, I must find him, and I will!
뭘! 이렇게 된 바 내가 뭐가 어떻게 되더라도 찾아 줄 테니까!
It's already good enough that he's not making a fuss.
이 이상 소란을 피우지 않으면 됐지.
The final match that you've been waiting for is about to begin!
자, 자, 기다리고 기다리셨던 결승전이 시작됩니다!
As we expected, it will be an one-time match of Jūbee Yagyū versus Kojirō the beautiful swordsman.
당사 예상대로 야규 주베와 미검사 코지로의 한판승부.
Who will win? Our company has the highest accuracy in Jipangu!
우승은 누구일까! 예상은 적중률 제일의 당사가 지팡구 제일이요!
Yes, here, here!
네, 여기요, 여기요!
Rather than Jūbee...
주베 님보다도 역시!
I bet on Koji!
코지 님이지!
-Koji is so cool! -Let me see!
-코지 님 정말 멋져! -보여줘, 보여줘!
I especially like his eyes!
이 눈이 좋아!
I wish Koji to win the match!
꼭 코지 님이 이겼으면 좋겠어!
Jūbee vs. Kojirō?
주베 대 코지로인가...
If one of them was Musashi, it could have been better.
누구든 무사시였으면 좋았을 텐데...
I know Kojirō too.
나도 코지로 씨는 알고 있어요.
You probably wanted to settle this with him, Musashi.
분명, 승부를 내고 싶었겠지요, 무사시 씨.
The final match of Jipangu Martial Arts Competition shall begin!
그럼 지금부터 지팡구 무예대회 결승전을 개시합니다!
Jūbee Yagyū!
야규 주베 님!
Mister Kojirō on the other side!
한쪽은 미스터 코지로 님!
It will be an one-game match.
승부는 단판 승부.
Kojirō. A young man with splendid martial arts skills.
코지로 님. 젊으면서도 대단한 무예 실력의 소유자다.
Jūbee. It is the first time facing a martial artist without a flaw.
주베 님. 처음으로 부족함이 없는 무예가하고 만났다.
Chance!
잡았다!
Yes, that's awesome!
이야... 대단하군.
You're so cool, Koji!
이야! 대단해, 코지 님!
Please! You must win this!
부탁이니 꼭 이겨요!
He is withstanding my attacks.
내 치기에 밀리지 않다니.
Jūbee is more than qualified to be called skilled at this rate.
지금 이것으로는 역시 주베 님이라고 말하기에 부족함이 없다.
He indeed is a man with extraordinary technique and talent.
확실히 기술도 자질도 비범한 사내.
But I can see him placing too much confidence in his youthfulness.
그러나, 젊음을 과신하는 것이 보인다.
Meanwhile, on Musashi...
그 쯤 무사시는...
Damn! Do whatever you want! Burn me or make a skew out of me-dasu!
젠장! 이렇게 될 거라면 굽든 꼬치를 만들어 먹든 마음대로!
No, I can't let that happen-dasu. If I die, everything is pop!
그러면 곤란하오. 죽으면 모든 건 펑.
Nothing shall stop me from getting out of this place-dasu!
뭐가 어떻게 되라도 여기서 나가 보이겠소!
The final match only had just begun, and yet it is about to end.
결승전은 시작되고, 금새 끝이 나려 하고 있었다.
Tsubamegaeshi.
츠바메가에시.
Interesting.
흥미롭구나.
Chance!
잡았다!
Yagyūshinkageryū Secret Sword.
야규신카게류 비검.
Tourō Nagashi!
등롱 띄우기!
Match set! Jūbee wins!
승부 났소이다! 주베 님의 승리!
Right, good job. A rare match of truly good quality.
그래, 훌륭하다. 정말 드물게 질 높은 시합이었다.
I am satisfied.
나는 만족이군.
I... lost...
내가... 졌다...
I, here, lost, now...
이 내가 진 것이다...
How come...
어째서인가...
What did I do wrong?
내 어디에 과실이...
Kojirō.
코지로 님.
While I won the match, it was an even match.
시합에서 이겼지만, 비등했습니다.
I admire your excellent swordsmanship.
훌륭한 칼솜씨, 감복했습니다.
Same goes for you, Jūbee.
주베 님이야말로.
Koji lost! I hate this!
코지 님이 졌어! 이런 건 싫어!
I'm so sad... I wanna die!
나 슬퍼... 죽고 싶어!
So Jūbee wins... Excellent job.
주베 님의 우승인가... 훌륭하군.
You really are superb.
역시 대단하오.
It seems that that damned Jūbee is trying to gain trust from Ieyasu and the power of shōgun following that.
주베 놈, 이걸로 점점 이에야스의 신망을 모아 쇼군의 힘을 얻겠다는 것 같다만...
But the time that you shall cry will come soon.
곧 울상을 지을 때가 꼭 온다.
And for that, I must exterminate that obstacle who knows my secret.
그것을 위해서도 내 비밀을 아는 그 방해자를 소멸해야만 한다.
From now on, we will begin the award ceremony of the 1st Jipangu Martial Arts Competition!
지금부터 제 1회 지팡구 무예 대회 우승자의 시상식을 실시합니다!
Meanwhile, at Hanzō's mansion...
그 쯤, 한조의 저택에서는...
Let me go! What are you going to do with me-dasu? Hey!
놓아! 어쩔 생각이냐! 이놈!
Musashi is about to be executed. Wait for the stormy latter half!
무사시의 처형히 집행되려 하고 있다. 질풍노도의 후반을 기다려라!
Yagyūshinkageryū Jūbee!
야규신카게류, 주베 님!
Champion. Yagyūshinkageryū Jūbee Yagyū.
우승. 야규신카게류 야규 주베.
You have displayed your excellent techniques at the 1st Jipangu Martial Art Competition.
귀공은 제 1회 지팡구 무예 대회에서 빼어난 기술을 모두에게 보여주었소.
Recognizing your championship, I award you with the certificate of award and 1,000 ryos as the cash prize.
우수하게 우승한 것을 인정하여 여기 상장 및 상금 천 량을 드리오이다.
Tho- thousand ryos?
천, 천 량이라고?
Awesome!
대단해!
Too bad!
젠장!
Could have been better if our brother won...
형이 우승했으면 좋았을 텐데.
Who's that guy?
뭐야, 저 사람?
Dad, we have a big problem!
아빠, 큰일이야!
Senhime!
센히메 님!
Move!
잠깐 비켜봐!
Senhime, we're in the middle of...
센히메, 지금 수상식의...
I'm sorry, but we have no time for that! Hanzō captured Musashi and took him to his mansion!
안됐지만 그럴 때가 아니야! 무사시 씨가 한조에게 잡혀서 저택에 끌려갔어!
Musashi?
무사시?
Oh, that man who had an extra match against Jūbee?
오, 주베하고 번외 시합을 했던 그 사내?
Please, rescue him right now.
부탁이야, 빨리 구해 줘.
Rescue him?
구한다니?
Aren't you a shōgun, grandpa? Aren't you supposed to be able to do anything?
할아버진 쇼군이잖아! 뭐라도 할 수 있는 거 아니야?
Calm down, Senhime. That man has committed treason!
진정해라, 센히메. 그 남자는 반역을 저질러서...
That's totally wrong! He was just late for the competition.
그러니까 그게 아니야. 그냥 무예 대회에 늦었을 뿐이야!
Even as a shōgun, pardoning someone who was wanted as a traitor would be...
그래도 내가 아무리 쇼군이라고 해도 반역자로 지명수배됐던 남자를...
What are you talking about? An innocent person is about to be executed!
뭔 소리야? 늦으면 무고한 사람이 사형돼!
B- but, listen...
그, 그래도 말야...
Shōgun!
쇼군!
I, Jūbee, have a request.
주베, 부탁드릴 것이 있습니다.
What is it, Jūbee?
뭔가, 주베?
Excuse me, but I will not receive the cash prize.
실례입니다만, 이번 보상금은 받지 않겠습니다.
What? Elaborate.
음? 무슨 소리인가?
Instead, I also ask for the rescue of Musashi.
그 대신, 무사시 님의 구출을 저도 부탁드립니다.
So, you'd forfeit your award and instead have me to help Musashi?
뭐라, 포상 대신 무사시를 도와라?
Musashi is a fine martial artist.
무사시 님은 훌륭한 무예가.
Again, I want to ask you to save that one person.
이대로 딱 한 분을 구해 주시기를 바라오니 부탁드립니다.
Jūbee!
주베 씨!
I request for that too!
소생도 부탁드리오이다!
Please, rescue Musashi by all means.
꼭 무사시 님을 구해 주십시오.
Musashi is a young man with a bright future! Rescue him!
무사시는 장래 있는 젊은이요! 구해 주시라!
Even that kind of man qualifies as a martial artist. Please save him.
그런 사내라도 무예가 축에는 낍니다. 구해 주기를 부탁드립니다.
If such a great number of people has the same request, then I must grant that request.
이 정도의 부탁이 있다면 알겠다. 들어 주겠어.
-Thank you, grandpa! -Hey, hey!
-할아버지, 고마워! -그래, 그래!
It's the end, Musashi.
끝이겠구나, 무사시.
Wh- what was that for-dasu?
뭐, 뭣이오, 방금은.
Iga Ninjutsu Sakuretsuya! You're next!
이하닌자술 작렬 화살! 다음은 너다!
I'm done for...
결국 나도...
Otsuru...
오츠루 씨...
I could not become the number one of Jipangu... this is so vexing-dasu...
나, 지팡구 제일이 되지 못하고... 분하오...
No. You must not die. Become the number one of Jipangu, Musashi!
안 돼요. 절대 죽으면 안 돼요! 지팡구 제일이 되세요, 무사시 씨!
Otsuru...
오츠루 씨...
Prepare for execution!
처형대 준비!
-Ruffians! -You're not doing as you want!
-불한당이다! -멋대로 하는 건 용서하지 못한다!
What's going on?
뭔 일이냐!
Kojirō! Ushiwaka! Everyone!
코지로! 우시와카! 모두!
How rude! What are you doing?
무례하다. 무슨 짓인가!
Jūbee.
주베 님.
Jūbee?
주베 씨?
First, I, Iga Ninja Hanzō, the shōgun's spy, own this mansion.
일단 이곳은 쇼군의 직속 밀정, 이하 닌자 한조의 저택이다.
Jūbee, I believe that even you will not let go a violent person.
설마 주베 님이라 하더라도 난폭한 자를 용서하시지는 않을 것.
The execution has been canceled.
처형은 취소되었다.
Unchain Musashi.
무사시 님의 사슬을 풀어 드려라.
What? That bastard is the traitor who defied the shōgun!
뭐시라? 녀석은 쇼군을 거슬러 반역을 저지른 천하의 반역자!
Did you lose your mind?
뭐에 눈이 뒤집혀 계시나?
It's an order!
명령이다!
See this warrant from Ieyasu!
이에야스 님의 문서다!
Th- there... there must be a mistake...
무, 무슨. 뭔가 착각이...
Silence! Are you questioning the document from the shōgun?
닥쳐라! 쇼군 직필 증명서를 의심하는가!
You will become the traitor instead!
그 쪽이야말로 반역자가 될 터이다!
How impudent! Lower your head!
건방지다! 숙여라!
Ye- yessir!
예, 예!
There's nothing to worry about anymore.
이제 걱정할 건 없어.
-Baiken! -What a relief!
-바이켄! -정말 다행이구나!
-Kojirō! -Stop that! That's embarrassing!
-코지로! -그만해라! 창피하다!
It was too close. Glad that we weren't too late.
위태로웠다. 시간을 겨우 맞춘 게 다행이었다.
Jūbee! I... I thank you, just like this-dasu!
주베 씨! 무사시... 무사시, 이대로이오!
I am so happy-dasu.
나, 행복하오.
I have never been as happy as right now-dasu!
이런 기쁜 일은 지금껏 없었소!
Is there a martial artist who cries loudly in front of people, Musashi?!
무예가라는 자가, 사람들 보는 앞에서 목놓고 우는 놈이 있나, 무사시!
This is not a tear-dasu! It's a sweat from eyes-dasu!
눈물이 아니오! 눈의 땀이오!
-Sweat of eyes...
-눈의 땀이오...
Rescued by the burning friendship of the swordsmen,
검사들의 뜨거운 우정에게 구해져
-Sweat of eyes isn't stopping-dasu...
-눈이 땀이 멈추질 않소...
Musashi was simply crying happily, without stubbornness nor grace.
지금은 더 이상 고집도 체면도 없이 단지 행복한 눈물을 흘릴 뿐인 무사시였다.
What a relief.
다행이구나.
Jūbee, you bastard...
네이놈, 주베 놈.
Since it came to this, I, Hanzō, swear to put Musashi into hell.
이렇게 된 바에는 이 한조가 무사시를 반드시 지옥으로 보내 주겠다.
All that looking for him, and yet we found nothing. Where could he have gone to?
이렇게 찾아도 발견하지 못하다니, 정말 어디에 갔을까요...
He wasn't in the competition too...
무예 대회에도 나오지 않고...
There will be a competition next year too.
무예 대회는 내년도 있다.
He'll just have to train harder for the coming year.
다음 1년도 열심히 수련하면 되겠구나.
Monk! Otsuru!
스님! 오츠루 씨!
Boss, you're rushing!
두목, 그렇게 황급히...
This is something I must rush to tell you!
이게 황급하게 알릴 일 아니면 뭐요!
I found him!
알아냈어요!
I found where Musashi is!
무사시 씨 어디 있는지 알아냈어!
Really?
정말로?
Wh- where?
어, 어디에?
Let's talk on the way.
걸어가면서 이야기하지.
Hurry up!
자! 서둘러!
Otsuru!
오츠루 씨...
Boss Zenigatan told me... I see you have gone through many things.
제니가탄 두목이... 여러 큰 일이 있었네요.
We did not call it a love yet
사랑이라 불러보지도 못하고
Yeah, that is...
응. 아, 저...
Being consistent is good, but that was too much.
한결같은 것도 좋지만, 이 무슨 너무한 일이니.
It's already time to part our ways
이별이 왔어요
There are a lot to talk about, so let's go back to the home and slowly do it!
쌓인 이야기도 있고 하니 집에 돌아가서 천천히!
Boss Zenigatan.
제니가탄 두목.
Musashi must go back to the castle now.
무사시 님은 이제 성으로 가야만 합니다.
Not much happened yesterday
아무렇지 않던 어제가
So...
그래서...
It's alright. I am relieved to see that healthy face of Musashi.
괜찮아요. 무사시 씨의 건강한 얼굴을 보니 안심되네요.
It's now a memory for two
둘의 추억
As we found out Musashi is all right, let's calm down and go back, Otsuru.
이걸로 마음을 다잡고 마을로 돌아가자꾸나, 오츠루.
Your profile of looking at the sunset
석양을 바라보는 당신의 옆모습
You'll get what you want next year, no matter what.
내년은 힘내요. 꼭.
Of course-dasu!
물론이오!
The belt that covered the love is tightening my heart
사랑을 숨긴 띠가 가슴을 조여온답니다
I'll do it safely and perfectly-dasu!
나, 건강하게 해내겠소!
Say hi to people in the village-dasu!
마을의 모두에게 전해주오!
Otsuru... I will do it...
오츠루 씨... 나, 꼭...
I won't cry or something
울지는 않아요
so don't worry
걱정하지 마세요
As much as you do
당신만큼이나
I'm living brightly
밝게 살고 있어요
I... I'll guard the granddaughter of the shōgun?
이, 이 내가 쇼군 님의 손녀님의 경호 역할?
Is that right-dasu?
인 것이오?
That's right. I shall entrust you with it.
그렇다. 신신당부하며 맡기겠다.
Uh...
아, 저...
Senhime will go on a tour across the empire.
센히메 님은 제국 만유의 길을 떠납니다.
You'll go with her.
그 길을 함께.
Ju- just a moment-dasu! I have an important objective to walk the road of swordsman...
자, 자, 잠깐 기다리시오. 나, 무사 수련의 길을 가야 할 소중한...
No. You do not have a say in this.
아니다. 아무쪼록 책임지지 않으면 안 된다.
No way...
그런...
Musashi.
무사시.
You heard Jūbee.
주베 님이 말한 대로다.
Ko- Kojirō, why are you here?!
코, 코지로, 왜 여기에?!
I have accepted the job as a guard for Senhime.
센히메 님의 경호 역할을 맡았다.
Guard job... then I'm...
경호 역할... 그럼 나는...
My assistant.
내 조수다.
Assistant?!
조수?!
Keep that in mind, and do not stray.
단단히 명심하고 붙어 다녀라.
Wh- why am I your assistant?!
왜, 왜 내가 네 조수로!
Senhime is here!
센히메 님!
Senhime?
센히메?
Senhime, I promise you that I will protect you, risking my life.
센히메 님, 이 코지로가 생명을 걸고 지켜드릴 것을 선언합니다.
Please do not worry.
부디 걱정하지 말아주십시오.
What's wrong, Musashi?
왜 그래요, 무사시 씨?
Se- Senhime...
세, 센히메라니...
No, that's...
아니, 그...
Ah, Senhime must be you.
아, 센히메라니 당신.
No, not that...
아, 아니, 그게 아니라...
So it was you, madam miss princess...
당신님이었던 것이오인 것이오?
Stop murmuring and remember your promise with me that you'll do me a favor if I let you watch the competition!
중얼거리지 말고, 무예 대회를 보여줬으면 뭐라도 내 말을 들어주겠다며!
A swordsman does not take his words back, you said!
무사가 두말은 안 한다고 했지?
Yes, right, that's of course!
네, 네, 그렇소! 그건 당연!
But... I... actually...
그래도 나... 사실은...
No, that is... that, right-dasu.
아니, 저... 그렇소.
I think I already know what's coming, but I guess it's inevitable.
앞날이 안 봐도 뻔하지만... 뭐, 어쩔 수 없나.
It's going to be an fun journey!
왠지 재밌는 여행이 될 거 같아!
Confused, Musashi will have to go on a journey. Really, what can be waiting for them? Look forward for the stormy journey!
어수선하게 여행을 떠나게 되어버린 무사시. 그것 참, 무엇이 기다리고 있는지 파란만장한 여행을 기대하시라.
Sometimes the moon jumps over
허공의 주머니에 달이
the pocket of empty sky
뛰어넘어가는 일도 있어
Laugh loudly and
큰 소리로 웃으면
morning will come tomorrow
내일에는 아침이 와
Don't worry too much about losing
잃는 것 따위는 아무것도 아니야
Keep going! Go for it!
계속 해나가! 앞으로 가!
A bare hand is strong
맨손은 강해
That's how it is! Let's go lightly
그런 거야! 가볍게 가자
That's how life is! Look, a chance
인생 그런 거야! 기회가 어라,
follows us wagging its tail!
꼬리를 흔들며 쫒아와!
That's how it is! Let's go lightly
그런 거야! 가볍게 가자
That's how the future is, too! Look, tomorrow
미래도 그런 거야! 내일이 어라,
is opening its hands and smiling at us!
양손을 벌리고 웃고 있어!
Jūbee, I'm so frustrated-dasu...
주베 씨, 나, 분하오...
I couldn't fight in the competition, and Kojirō and Baiken took my place-dasu!
무예 대회에 나가지 못하고 코지로나 바이켄에게 순위를 빼앗겼소!
What should I do from now on, to become the number one martial artist of Jipangu-dasu?
누가 뭐래도 지팡구 제일의 무예가가 되려면 지금 이후로 어떻게 해야 하오?
Dual Blade? What is that?
이도류? 그것이 무엇이오?
Next story! Hundred Matches in Musashi's Dreams
다음 이야기! 무사시, 꿈의 백번승부이오
Watch the stormy yet excellent matches-dasu!
질풍노도의 명승부를 보시오!
Next Episode
다음 이야기
Hundred Matches
무사시, 꿈의 백번승부
in Musashi’s Dreams
기대하세요!